https://www.populationconnection.org/us/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At Population Connection, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process donations and to provide a more personalized membership experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When you donate, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your donation.
How does Population Connection protect customer information?
When you donate, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
What about “cookies”?
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent that.
Will Population Connection disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
Population Connection and Population Connection Action Fund as sister organizations may share your personal information with each other. We may also occasionally exchange or rent your name and postal address with trustworthy third parties (other non-profit organizations). We do not otherwise share your personal information with outside organizations. You can instruct us not to rent or exchange your name and postal address with a third party at any time by emailing us at info@popconnect.org or by calling 800-767-1956.
Your consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information at your discretion by Population Connection. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
We Are Population Connection
Since 1968, Population Connection (formerly Zero Population Growth or ZPG) has been America's voice for population stabilization—we are the largest grassroots population organization in the United States! As a 501(c)(3) charity, all donations made to us are tax-deductible.
Already a member? Renew today!
Your tax-deductible membership dues help us advocate for universal access to birth control, educate tomorrow’s leaders about global population challenges, and mobilize Americans who care about stabilizing population. Your on-going support is vital to our continued success!
Renew Today
Stay Updated
Join our Email Action Network to hear about important legislative developments, constituent calls to action, and events in your area!
Email: Required
Yes, I would like to receive e-mail from Population Connection
Spam Control Text:
Please leave this field empty
Employment
Privacy Policy
State Disclosures
Contact Us
Follow Us
Facebook
Twitter
© Population Connection 2020. 2120 L St NW, Suite
500 Washington, D.C. 20037
CLOSE
Host a Table
Fill out your information and your Population Connection coordinator will contact you with ideas for hosting an informational table in your community!
Name
First
Last
CityStateEmail
MessageCAPTCHACommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
CLOSE
Connect with Our Team
Please get in touch with me so I can learn about ways to raise awareness about the importance of population stabilization.
Name
First
Last
CityStateEmail
MessageCAPTCHAPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
CLOSE
[item.name][item.name][item][item]
